Guide to the Arlen Specter Senatorial Papers, Group 6. Public Relations and Media Files, 1972-2010 TJU.2010.01.06
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Media Appearances, 1972-2010; II.
  - Daily Compilation; Commerce Hearing: Introduction of Dean Ornish; Floor: Iraq Supplemental, September 30, 2003 (Box 1164, Video 1)
  - Floor Statement: Iraq Funding, September 30, 2003 (Box 1164, Video 2)
  - Daily Compilation; NBC Today Show: CIA Identity Leak; Floor: Iraq Supplemental, October 1, 2003 (Box 1164, Video 3)
  - Floor Statement, October 1, 2003 (Box 1164, Video 4-5)
  - NBC Today Show: CIA Operative Identity Leak, October 1, 2003 (Box 1164, Video 6)
  - Daily Compilation; Fox News: CIA Leak, October 2, 2003 (Box 1164, Video 7)
  - Fox News, October 2, 2003 (Box 1164, Video 8)
  - CNN Late Edition with Senator Levin; CIA Operative Identity Leak/Syria, October 5, 2003 (Box 1164, Video 9-10)
  - PA Newsmakers, October 7, 2003 (Box 1164, Video 11)
  - Daily Compilation, October 8, 2003 (Box 1164, Video 12)
  - Citizens for Arlen Specter: Focus Group, October 14, 2003 (Box 1164, Video 13)
  - Daily Compilation; Pennsylvania Newsmakers: Current Events, October 14, 2003 (Box 1164, Video 14)
  - Citizens for Arlen Specter: Focus Group, October 15, 2003 (Box 1164, Video 15)
  - Daily Compilation; Judiciary Hearing: Nominations, October 15, 2003 (Box 1164, Video 16)
  - Judiciary Hearing: Fisher, October 15, 2003 (Box 1164, Video 17)
  - Specter Ad Dial Groups: Harrisburg PA, Overlays, October 15, 2003 (Box 1164, Video 18)
  - Daily Compilation; Floor: Iraq Supplemental; Judiciary Executive: Immigration, October 16, 2003 (Box 1164, Video 19)
  - Floor Statement, October 16, 2003 (Box 1164, Video 20-21)
  - Judiciary Executive Hearing, October 16, 2003 (Box 1164, Video 22)
  - Fox and Friends, October 17, 2003 (Box 1164, Video 23)
  - Daily Compilation; Judiciary Hearing: Janice Rodgers Brown; Floor: Hardiman Nomination, October 22, 2003 (Box 1164, Video 24)
  - Floor Statement, October 22, 2003 (Box 1164, Video 25)
  - Judiciary Hering: Janice Brown, Opening Statement, October 22, 2003 (Box 1164, Video 26-27)
  - Daily Compilation; C-SPAN, Washington Journal: Current Events, October 23, 2003 (Box 1164, Video 28)
  - Judiciary Executive, October 23, 2003 (Box 1164, Video 29)
  - Washington Journal, October 23, 2003 (Box 1164, Video 30)
  - Daily Compilation; Judiciary Hearing: monopsony, October 23, 2003 (Box 1164, Video 31)
  - Judiciary Hearing, October 30, 2003 (Box 1164, Video 32)
  - Project 2000, October 30, 2003 (Box 1164, Video 33)
  - Daily Compilation; LHHS Hearing: Palestinian Education Materials, November 4, 2003 (Box 1164, Video 34)
  - Floor Statement, November 5, 2003 (Box 1164, Video 35)
  - Joint Economic Committee, November 5, 2003 (Box 1164, Video 36)
  - Daily Compilation; Joint Economic Committee: Tax Reform, Flat Tax; Floor: Agriculture Appropriations (2 Days); Judiciary Executive: Janice Rodgers Brown Nomination, November 6, 2003 (Box 1164, Video 37)
  - Floor Statement: AG, November 6, 2003 (Box 1164, Video 38)
  - Judiciary Executive Meeting, November 6, 2003 (Box 1165, Video 1)
  - KDKA and WTAE, November 5-6, 2003 (Box 1165, Video 2)
  - P.A.R.F. Rally for Independence, November 6-7, 2003 (Box 1165, Video 3)
  - Pittsburgh Press Conference: Intelligence Memo; Press Conference: Judicial Nominations; Floor: Veterans' Day and Syrian Accountability Act, November 11, 2003 (Box 1165, Video 4)
  - Floor Statement, November 11, 2003 (Box 1165, Video 5)
  - CNN, November 12, 2003 (Box 1165, Video 6)
  - Floor Statement, November 12, 2003 (Box 1165, Video 7)
  - Daily Compilation; Floor: Judicial Nominations (2); CNN Crossfire: Judicial Nominations, November 13, 2003 (Box 1165, Video 8)
  - Floor Statement, November 13, 2003 (Box 1165, Video 9)
  - Daily Compilation; Floor: Saudi Accountability Act and Polio Awareness, November 18, 2003 (Box 1165, Video 10)
  - Floor Statement, November 18, 2003 (Box 1165, Video 11)
  - JFK Assassination, November 18 and 20, 2003 (Box 1165, Video 12-13)
  - CBS, November 20, 2003 (Box 1165, Video 14)
  - CNN, November 20, 2003 (Box 1165, Video 15)
  - Judiciary Hearing, November 20, 2003 (Box 1165, Video 16)
  - NBC, November 20, 2003 (Box 1165, Video 17)
  - CBS The Early Show: JFK Assassination Conspiracy Theories, November 21, 2003 (Box 1165, Video 18)
  - Duquesne University Pittsburgh: Revisiting the Warren Commission, November 22, 2003 (Box 1165, Video 19)
  - President Bush in Pittsburgh, December 2, 2003 (Box 1165, Video 20-23)
  - Channel 3: Kenny Walker Shooting News, December 10, 2003 (Box 1165, Video 24)
  - Specter Amendment S. 2720, 2003 (Box 1165, Video 25)
  - Floor Statement: Reid Amendment to Labor-HHS Appropriations Bill, 2003 (Box 1165, Video 26)
  - Cantwell Amendment H.R. 2673, 2003 (Box 1165, Video 27)
  - Confirmation of Miguel Estrado, 2003 (Box 1165, Video 28)
  - Fox News: Iraq, 2003 (Box 1165, Video 29)
  - Nightline: Republican Tax Cuts, 2003 (Box 1165, Video 30)
  - PA Newsmakers: Toomey, 2003 (Box 1165, Video 31)
  - PCN Call-In: Senator Arlen Specter, 2003 (Box 1165, Video 32)
  - Local CBS: Save MCP - Medical College of PA Hospital Closing, 2003 (Box 1165, Video 33)
  - Senate's Subcommittee on Terrorism, Technology, and Homeland Security, 2003 (Box 1165, Video 34)
  - Fox News: Specter on Iraq Resolution, 2003 (Box 1165, Video 35-36)
  - WNED Scranton, 2003 (Box 1165, Video 37)
  - WVIA Call-In with Santorum, 2003 (Box 1165, Video 38)
  - WYOU Scranton, 2003 (Box 1165, Video 39)
  - 03-D-06; 03-D-07, 2003 (Box 1165, Video 40-41)
  - Floor Statement, January 4, 2004 (Box 1166, Video 1)
  - Campaign Kick-Off, January 8-9, 2004 (Box 1166, Video 2-3)
  - Floor Statement, January 20, 2004 (Box 1166, Video 4)
  - LHHS Hearing: Overtime, January 20, 2004 (Box 1166, Video 5)
  - Judiciary Hearing: Pratter, January 22, 2004 (Box 1166, Video 6)
  - LHHS Hearing: NIH Conflict, January 22, 2004 (Box 1166, Video 7)
  - Judiciary Executive: Van Antwerpe, January 28, 2004 (Box 1166, Video 8)
  - CNN Wolf Blitzer: Senator Arlen Specter, January 30, 2004 (Box 1166, Video 9)
  - Citizens for Arlen Specter: Rudy, February 10, 2004 (Box 1166, Video 10)
  - Judiciary Hearing, February 11, 2004 (Box 1166, Video 11)
  - Floor Statement, February 12, 2004 (Box 1166, Video 12-14)
  - Judiciary Executive, February 26, 2004 (Box 1166, Video 15)
  - Senator Arlen Specter Boeing Philadelphia Raw Camera Wide, March 8, 2004 (Box 1166, Video 16)
  - Judiciary Executive, March 11, 2004 (Box 1166, Video 17)
  - Judiciary Hearing, March 23-24, 2004 (Box 1166, Video 18-20)
  - LHHS Hearing, March 25, 2004 (Box 1166, Video 21)
  - LHHS Hearing, April 1, 2004 (Box 1166, Video 22)
  - Primary Debate, April 3, 2004 (Box 1166, Video 23)
  - Pittsburgh News Coverage: Shippingsport Nuclear Plant Visit Campaign, April 5, 2004 (Box 1166, Video 24)
  - Judiciary Hearing: OPEC, April 7, 2004 (Box 1166, Video 25)
  - Senator Specter Penn State Visit, April 14, 2004 (Box 1166, Video 26-27)
  - NBC ID Live at Issue WCAU-TV Philadelphia, April 18, 2004 (Box 1166, Video 28)
  - NBC Nightly news, April 25, 2004 (Box 1166, Video 29)
  - Johnstown, Erie, April 26, 2004 (Box 1166, Video 30)
  - KDKA-TV (CBS) Pittsburgh Eyewitness News, April 26, 2004 (Box 1166, Video 31)
  - Senator Arlen Specter, April 26, 2004 (Box 1166, Video 32)
  - ABC News 27 at 6 WHTM-TV, Channel 11 News at 6 WPXI-TV NBC: Campaign, April 27, 2004 (Box 1166, Video 33)
  - News Clips: 2004 Primary, April 27, 2004 (Box 1166, Video 34)
  - GAC Hearing with Ridge, May 1, 2004 (Box 1166, Video 35)
  - Floor Statement, May 4, 2004 (Box 1166, Video 36)
  - LHHS Hearing: Overtime, May 4, 2004 (Box 1166, Video 37)
  - Floor Statement, May 11, 2004 (Box 1166, Video 38-40)
  - Daily Compilation; Floor Statement: Trial of Saddam Hussein, May 18, 2004 (Box 1166, Video 41)
  - Judiciary Hearing, May 20, 2004 (Box 1166, Video 42)
  - CNN: State Funeral for President Ronald Reagan, June 9, 2004 (Box 1166, Video 43)
  - Daily Compilation; Fox News Day Six: Stem Cell Research, June 9, 2004 (Box 1166, Video 44)
  - Daily Compilation; Floor Statement: Juan Sanchez, June 23, 2004 (Box 1166, Video 45)
  - Appropriations Hearing, June 24, 2004 (Box 1166, Video 46)
  - Daily Compilation; Judiciary Executive: DOJ Documents; Transportation Appropriations Hearing: Airline Security, June 24, 2004 (Box 1166, Video 47)
  - Senator Specter, January-June 2004 (Box 1166, Video 48)
  - Dr. Harold Gullan on First Fathers: Father's Day, C-SPAN II, June 2004 (Box 1166, Video 49)
  - MSNBC, July 9, 2004 (Box 1166, Video 50)
  - Harrisburg Local Coverage/National: Campbelltown Tornado, July 16, 2004 (Box 1167, Video 1)
  - NBC Today Show: Intelligence Reform Bill, July 18, 2004 (Box 1167, Video 2)
  - Fox and Friends: Intelligence Reform Bill, July 21, 2004 (Box 1167, Video 3)
  - Press Conference: 9/11 Commission Report, July 22, 2004 (Box 1167, Video 4)
  - PBS NewsHour with Lehrer: Intelligence Reform Bill, July 30, 2004 (Box 1167, Video 5)
  - CNN: Intelligence Reform Bill, July 30, 2004 (Box 1167, Video 6)
  - Fox and Friends: Intelligence Reform Bill, July 31, 2004 (Box 1167, Video 7)
  - KDKA Pittsburgh: Specter and Airport Security, August 19, 2004 (Box 1167, Video 8)
  - PBS NewsHour, August 24, 2004 (Box 1167, Video 9)
  - Erie Local Coverage, August 25, 2004 (Box 1167, Video 10)
  - Fox News Sunday: Arlen Specter Spotlight, September 5, 2004 (Box 1167, Video 11)
  - MSNBC Hardball: Intelligence Reform Bill, September 7, 2004 (Box 1167, Video 12-13)
  - C-SPAN: Press Conference, September 7, 2004 (Box 1167, Video 14)
  - Fox News: Cheney/NASA, September 8, 2004 (Box 1167, Video 15)
  - Daily Compilation; Fox News, GAC Hearing, Floor Statement, September 8, 2004 (Box 1167, Video 16)
  - Washington Journal, September 9, 2004 (Box 1167, Video 17)
  - Citizens for Arlen Specter: 11 Focus Group Spots, September 12, 2004 (Box 1167, Video 18)
  - Daily Compilation; Senate Commerce Committee: Wireless 411 Legislation, September 21, 2004 (Box 1167, Video 19)
  - Floor Statement, September 28, 2004 (Box 1167, Video 20-21)
  - CNN: 2004 Presidential Debate, September 30, 2004 (Box 1167, Video 22-23)
  - General Election Debate, October 2, 2004 (Box 1167, Video 24-27)
  - Daily Compilation; Floor Statement: Chambliss Amendment; Floor Statement: McCain Amendment, October 7, 2004 (Box 1167, Video 28-29)
  - Judiciary Hearing, October 8, 2004 (Box 1167, Video 30)
  - Presidential Debate, October 8, 2004 (Box 1167, Video 31)
  - General Election Debate, October 9, 2004 (Box 1167, Video 32-33)
  - Senate Debate: Philadelphia, October 9, 2004 (Box 1167, Video 34)
  - News Makers: Arlen Specter, October 12, 2004 (Box 1167, Video 35)
  - CNN: 2004 Presidential Debate at Arizona State University, October 13, 2004 (Box 1167, Video 36)
  - Patriot News: Ed Board, October 17, 2004 (Box 1167, Video 37)
  - Citizens for Arlen Specter: Fox, Barsh, Stereo Mix, October 26, 2004 (Box 1167, Video 38)
  - Daily Compilation: CNN, Fox News, CBS, November 8, 2004 (Box 1167, Video 39)
  - WPGH, November 9, 2004 (Box 1167, Video 40)
  - CNN: American Morning; Fox: Dayside, November 12, 2004 (Box 1167, Video 41)
  - Fox News, November 12, 2004 (Box 1167, Video 42)
  - CBS: Evening News, November 16, 2004 (Box 1168, Video 1)
  - Action News; This Week; CBS Evening News, November 3-16, 2004 (Box 1168, Video 2)
  - Philadelphia/National coverage - WPVI, ABC This Week, CBS Evening News: Judges, November 3-16, 2004 (Box 1168, Video 3)
  - C-SPAN Press Conference: Judicial Chairmanship, November 18, 2004 (Box 1168, Video 4-5)
  - Daily Compilation; Floor Statement: Intel Bill, December 8, 2004 (Box 1168, Video 6)
  - PCN Call-In: Senator Arlen Specter, 2004 (Box 1168, Video 7)
  - Presidential Election 2004: Bucks County Town Hall (Box 1168, Video 8)
  - Primary Reelection, 2004 (Box 1168, Video 9)
  - State of Pennsylvania #215: Arlen Specter, 2004 (Box 1168, Video 10)
  - Swearing In, January 4, 2005 (Box 1168, Video 11-13)
  - ABC, CBS, NBC Nightly News, January 6, 2005 (Box 1168, Video 14)
  - CNN Late Edition, January 6, 2005 (Box 1168, Video 15)
  - Gonzales Hearing, January 6, 2005 (Box 1168, Video 16-17)
  - CNN America Morning: Gonzales Hearing, January 7, 2005 (Box 1168, Video 18)
  - CNN: Inside Politics, January 7, 2005 (Box 1168, Video 19)
  - Fox and Friends: Gonzales Hearing, January 7, 2005 (Box 1168, Video 20)
  - NBC Today Show: Gonzales Hearing, January 7, 2005 (Box 1168, Video 21)
  - Elwyn in the News: Marines visit KDC, January 10, 2005 (Box 1168, Video 22)
  - Asbstos Hearings, January 11, 2005 (Box 1168, Video 23)
  - 20 minutes Round Alita, January 11, 2005 (Box 1168, Video 24)
  - Judiciary Committee Executive: Gonzales/Asbestos, January 19, 2005 (Box 1168, Video 25)
  - Fox and Friends: Gonzales, January 26, 2005 (Box 1168, Video 26-28)
  - PBS NewsHour: Gonzales, January 26, 2005 (Box 1168, Video 29)
  - CNN American Morning: Gonzales, January 27, 2005 (Box 1168, Video 30)
  - Judiciary Executive Meeting: Gonzales Nomination, January 27, 2005 (Box 1168, Video 31)
  - Beth Nolan Testimony on Alito Nomination, January 2005 (Box 1168, Video 32)
  - Lou Dobbs Tonight: SOTU, February 2, 2005 (Box 1168, Video 33)
  - C-SPAN Washington Journal, February 3, 2005 (Box 1168, Video 34-35)
  - Judiciary Hearing: Bankruptcy Reform Legislation, February 10, 2005 (Box 1168, Video 36)
  - C-SPAN Press Conference: Judiciary 1st 6 weeks/Agenda, February 24, 2005 (Box 1168, Video 37-38)
  - Specter News Conference, February 24, 2005 (Box 1168, Video 39)
  - CNN Late Edition: Judicial Nominations/Specter Health, February 27, 2005 (Box 1168, Video 40-41)
  - Judiciary Hearing: Thomas Griffith Nomination, March 8, 2005 (Box 1168, Video 42-43)
  - CNN Inside Politics: Judicial Security Nominations, March 14, 2005 (Box 1168, Video 44)
  - NBC: Bolton Confirmation News, March 15, 2005 (Box 1168, Video 45)
  - Judiciary Hearing: Telecom Mergers, March 15, 2005 (Box 1168, Video 46)
  - Judiciary Executive Meeting: Myers Nomination, March 17, 2005 (Box 1168, Video 47)
  - CNN Wolf Blitzer: Terri Schiavo, March 22, 2005 (Box 1169, Video 1)
  - Judiciary Hearing: Patriot Act Renewal, April 5, 2005 (Box 1169, Video 2-3)
  - Judiciary Executive Meeting: Nominations, April 7, 2005 (Box 1169, Video 4)
  - Press Conference: Patriot/Asbestos, April 12, 2005 (Box 1169, Video 5-6)
  - Judiciary Hearing: Identity Theft, April 13, 2005 (Box 1169, Video 7)
  - Judiciary Executive Meeting: Nominations, April 14, 2005 (Box 1169, Video 8)
  - PBS NewsHour: Nuclear/Const. Option on Judicial Nominations, April 18, 2005 (Box 1169, Video 9)
  - Specter Biography, April 19, 2005 (Box 1169, Video 10)
  - CNN Inside Politics: Judges, April 21, 2005 (Box 1169, Video 11)
  - Floor: Independence, April 21, 2005 (Box 1169, Video 12)
  - Press Conference: Stem Cell, April 21, 2005 (Box 1169, Video 13)
  - CNN Late Edition with Leahy Bolton: Nominations; Nuclear Option, April 24, 2005 (Box 1169, Video 14-15)
  - Bloomberg News: Asbestos/Judges, April 26, 2005 (Box 1169, Video 16)
  - Defense Appropriations Hearing: DoD Funding/BRAC with Rumsfeld, April 27, 2005 (Box 1169, Video 17)
  - Judiciary Hearing: Asbestos Legislation, April 27-28, 2005 (Box 1169, Video 18-20)
  - Judiciary Hearing: USA Patriot Act, May 10, 2005 (Box 1169, Video 21)
  - Judiciary Executive: 2pm Session, May 11, 2005 (Box 1169, Video 22)
  - Judiciary Executive: Pryor Nomination/Asbestos, May 12, 2005 (Box 1169, Video 23)
  - NBC Today Show: Segment on Senator Specter, May 13, 2005 (Box 1169, Video 24)
  - CNN Inside Politics: Judges, May 18, 2005 (Box 1169, Video 25)
  - Judiciary Committee: Courthouse Security, May 18, 2005 (Box 1169, Video 26)
  - Judiciary Markup: Asbestos, May 19, 2005 (Box 1169, Video 27)
  - NINA Totenberg/Arlen Specter, May 19, 2005 (Box 1169, Video 28)
  - Judges, May 20, 2005 (Box 1169, Video 29)
  - Floor Statement: Judges, May 24, 2005 (Box 1169, Video 30)
  - SRC Press Conference: Judges, May 24, 2005 (Box 1169, Video 31)
  - Judiciary Executive: Asbestos, May 25, 2005 (Box 1169, Video 32)
  - C-SPAN 3 Press Conference: Stem Cell Legislation, May 25, 2005 (Box 1169, Video 33)
  - Judiciary Executive: Asbestos, May 26, 2005 (Box 1169, Video 34-35)
  - Lou Dobbs Tonight: Stem Cells/Asbestos, May 26, 2005 (Box 1169, Video 36)
  - ABC This Week, May 29, 2005 (Box 1169, Video 37)
  - CBS Evening News: Stem Cells, June 3, 2005 (Box 1169, Video 38)
  - Specter News Clips, May - June 8, 2005 (Box 1169, Video 39)
  - Judiciary Executive: Judges Legislation, June 9, 2005 (Box 1169, Video 40)
  - CNN Inside Politics: Detainee Hearing, June 15, 2005 (Box 1169, Video 41)
  - C-SPAN Judiciary Hearings: Detainees, June 15, 2005 (Box 1169, Video 42-43)
  - Judiciary Executive, June 16, 2005 (Box 1169, Video 44)
  - Floor: Asbestos, June 23, 2005 (Box 1170, Video 1)
  - Floor: Democrats' Letter to Bush, June 23, 2005 (Box 1170, Video 2)
  - Press Files, June 29, 2005 (Box 1170, Video 3-4)
  - Judiciary Executive, June 30, 2005 (Box 1170, Video 5)
  - Fox News/C-SPAN: O'Conner Resignation; Meet the Press, CNN Late Edition, This Week; PBS NewsHour, July 1-6, 2005 (Box 1170, Video 6)
  - PBS NewsHour: Supreme Court Vacancy, July 6, 2005 (Box 1170, Video 7)
  - PBS NewsHour: Supreme Court Vacancy; BRAC Hearing, July 6-7, 2005 (Box 1170, Video 8)
  - BRAC Hearing, July 7, 2005 (Box 1170, Video 9)
  - CBS Face the Nation: Supreme Court Vacancy, Stem Cells, July 10, 2005 (Box 1170, Video 10-11)
  - LHHS Hearing: PBS Funding, July 11, 2005 (Box 1170, Video 12)
  - CNN: Inside Politics, July 12, 2005 (Box 1170, Video 13)
  - C-SPAN Press Conference, July 12, 2005 (Box 1170, Video 14-16)
  - Floor: Asbestos; C-SPAN White House Press Conference, June 23 and July 12, 2005 (Box 1170, Video 17)
  - NBC Nightly: Stem Cells, July 12, 2005 (Box 1170, Video 18)
  - LHHS: Stem Cells, July 12, 2005 (Box 1170, Video 19)
  - Judiciary Hearing: Habeas Corpus (Audio only), July 13, 2005 (Box 1170, Video 20)
  - CNN: Lou Dobbs, July 14, 2005 (Box 1170, Video 21-22)
  - Judiciary Markup, July 14, 2005 (Box 1170, Video 23)
  - Judiciary Executive: Patriot Act, July 21, 2005 (Box 1170, Video 24)
  - ABC World News Tonight: Senator Specter, July 25, 2005 (Box 1170, Video 25)
  - Judiciary Hearing: Immigration, July 26, 2005 (Box 1170, Video 26-27)
  - Floor: Frist and Stem Cells, July 29, 2005 (Box 1170, Video 28)
  - Senator Specter News Clips, June-July 2005 (Box 1170, Video 29)
  - Specter News Clips, June 9 - August 12, 2005 (Box 1170, Video 30)
  - GTMO, DV Visit Guantanamo Bay, Cuba, August 15, 2005 (Box 1170, Video 31)
  - Fox News, August 25, 2005 (Box 1170, Video 32)
  - C-SPAN with Brian Lamb, August 26, 2005 (Box 1170, Video 33)
  - C-SPAN Press Conference, September 6, 2005 (Box 1170, Video 34)
  - C-SPAN: Q and A; NBC: MTP on Roberts, September 4 and 11, 2005 (Box 1170, Video 35)
  - This Week with George Stephanopolous, September 9, 2005 (Box 1170, Video 36)
  - Judiciary Committee Hearing: John Roberts Nomination, September 12-13, 2005 (Box 1170, Video 37-49)
  - NBC Nightly News, September 13, 2005 (Box 1170, Video 50)
  - Senator Arlen Specter DVD Compilation; CNN Profile: Ed Henry; NBC Nightly News with Brian Williams, September 13, 2005 (Box 1170, Video 51)
  - NBC Chris Matthews Show: Specter profile; CBS Face the Nation: Roberts Nomination (with Leahy), September 18, 2005 (Box 1170, Video 52)
  - Floor Statement, September 19, 2005 (Box 1170, Video 53)
  - Federal Bar Association Annual meeting and Convention, September 22, 2005 (Box 1170, Video 54)
  - Floor Statement: Judge Roberts and Televising the Supreme Court, September 26, 2005 (Box 1170, Video 55)
  - Floor Statement: Intelligence Reporting and Iraq; Floor Statements: National Intelligence Director, July 22 and September 28-29, 2005 (Box 1170, Video 56)
  - Floor Statement: Roberts and Televising the Supreme Court; Floor Statement: Democratic Filibuster; Veterans Committee: Introduction of Tuerk; Floor Statement: Roberts; CNN: Press Conference, September 26-30, 2005 (Box 1170, Video 57)
  - The Miers Nomination; C-SPAN: Mansfield Room; C-SPAN: Press Conference, October 3, 2005 (Box 1170, Video 58)
  - Senator Arlen Specter, October 9, 2005 (Box 1170, Video 59)
  - Judiciary Committee Hearing, October 18, 2005 (Box 1170, Video 60)
  - LHHS Hearing: Stem Cells; Judiciary Hearing: Reporter Shield; C-SPAN 3: Specter/Leahy Press Conference on Miers Nomination, October 19, 2005 (Box 1170, Video 61)
  - Judiciary Committee Hearing, October 20, 2005 (Box 1170, Video 62)
  - Floor Statement: LHHS Bill and Stem Cells, October 21, 2005 (Box 1170, Video 63)
  - CBS Face the Nation with Senator Feinstein: Miers Nomination, October 23, 2005 (Box 1170, Video 64)
  - Floor Statement Compiliation: LHHS Appropriations Bill, October 24, 2005 (Box 1170, Video 65)
  - Floor Compilation, October 25, 2005 (Box 1170, Video 66-68)
  - PBS NewsHour with Jim Lehrer: Miers with Senator Leahy, October 26, 2005 (Box 1170, Video 69)
  - Floor Statement: Miers, October 27, 2005 (Box 1170, Video 70)
  - Senator Arlen Specter, October 30, 2005 (Box 1170, Video 71)
  - CNN Late Edition: Libby and Miers, October 30, 2005 (Box 1170, Video 72)
  - Alito Rollout; Mansfield Room; Press Conference, October 31, 2005 (Box 1170, Video 73)
  - Senator Specter, August-October 2005 (Box 1170, Video 74)
  - Senator Specter: Chester Dinner, October 2005 (Box 1170, Video 75-76)
  - Presidential signing statements, 2005 (Box 1170, Video 77-78)
  - C-SPAN 3: Specter/Leahy Press Conference; FOX News Coverage of Press Conference; Floor Statement: H1B Visas, November 3, 2005 (Box 1171, Video 1)
  - Judiciary: Terrorism Finance Hearing, November 8, 2005 (Box 1171, Video 2)
  - Judiciary Subcommittee: Marriage Amendment; Judiciary: TV in Supreme Court; Floor Statements (3): Habeas Corpus, November 9 and 15, 2005 (Box 1171, Video 3)
  - Judiciary Committee, November 16, 2005 (Box 1171, Video 4)
  - Floor Speech, November 17, 2005 (Box 1171, Video 5)
  - Judiciary Committee, November 17, 2005 (Box 1171, Video 6-7)
  - Senate Floor Coverage, December 15, 2005 (Box 1171, Video 8)
  - Floor Statements: LHHS; Press Conference: Alito; Press Conference: Patriot Act; Floor Statement: Patriot Act; CNN AM: Patriot Act, November 18 - December 15, 2005 (Box 1171, Video 9)
  - Floor Statements (8): Patriot Act, December 16, 2005 (Box 1171, Video 10)
  - Floor Statements, Fox, CNN Late Edition: Patriot Act, December 14-18, 2005 (Box 1171, Video 11)
  - Floor Discussion: Patriot Act and Deficit Reduction Bill, 2005 (Box 1171, Video 12-13)
  - PCN: Journalists Roundtable with Specter, John Micek, Brott Lieberman, John Baer, 2005 (Box 1171, Video 14)
  - PCN: Rendell/Specter Ag. Event, 2005 (Box 1171, Video 15)
  - C-SPAN/Fox News: Roberts Confirmation, S. 397, 2005 (Box 1171, Video 16)
  - C. J. Roberts Media clips, 2005 (Box 1171, Video 17)
  - JudgeRoberts.com; "Brilliant" TV Ad; PFA Roberts Ad Launch Memo; What People Are Saying Memo; Supreme Court Nomination Packet, 2005 (Box 1171, Video 18)
  - Roberts Confirmation Compilation: Opening Statement; Swearing-in; Day 1 Post-Hearing Gaggle; Arlen and Joan: Behind the Dias; 1st Round of Questioning; Day 2 Post-Hearing Gaggle; 2nd Round of Questioning; Day 3 Post-Hearing Gaggle; Closing Statement, 2005 (Box 1171, Video 19)
  - Judiciary Committee Hearing, January 6, 2006 (Box 1171, Video 20)
  - CBS Sunday, January 8, 2006 (Box 1171, Video 21)
  - Judiciary Committee Hearing: Samuel Alito Nomination, January 9, 2006 (Box 1171, Video 22)
  - Monday, January 9, 2006 (Box 1171, Video 23)
  - Alito Opening Statement; Alito Swearing In; ABC: World News Tonight; CBS: Face the Nation; CNN: Late Edition, January 8 and 9, 2006 (Box 1171, Video 24)
  - Senator Arlen Specter Alito Hearing Day 1, January 9, 2006 (Box 1171, Video 25)